New York State Board of Mediation Cases 5581
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A 9101 - A 9499 (1948). (Box 37)
  - Seaboard Furniture Manufacturers., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Segalock Fasteners, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - World Store Equipment Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Art Craft Upholstery Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - 1868 Holland Ave, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Chickenland, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Chas. S. Cher Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - 1482-6 Southern Boulevard, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - American Furniture Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Peerless Hotel, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Queens Bridge Bakery, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Ward Banking Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Greater NY Photo Finishers Assn., Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - 1921 Avenue K, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - 2816 Cortland Street, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Ludwig Baumann, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Pur-All Paint Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Trubek Labs, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Unz and Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - 1737 Pilgrim Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - 1845 82nd Street, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - 1133 Findlay Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - 130 West 228th St., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - 1963-1985 Bryant Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - 20 East 190th Street, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Weil Furniture Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Miller's Furniture Market, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Rubin Dental Lab, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Scotty's Service Station, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Super Metal Mfg. Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Triboro Coach Corp., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - 260 Ocean Parkway, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - 1283 Morris Ave, Bronx, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - title Guaranty and Trust Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - Coldwell-Philadelphia Div. of Portable Prod. Corp., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - Independent Retail Paint Dealers, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - Namm Store, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - Metropolitan Embossing Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - 2518-20 Webb Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - Pechter Baking Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - American Zyloptic Co, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - Hermes Engravers, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - Marval Curtain Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corp., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - 63 West 139th Street, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  - 1820 Loring Place, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 71)
  - Video Television, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 72)
  - Venice Upholstery, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 73)
  - 2700 Kingsbridge Terrace, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 74)
  - American Fig and Date Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 75)
  - Janaug, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 76)
  - Saks and Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 77)
  - W. Cabble Excelsior Wire Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 78)
  - Childs Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 79)
  - Continental Baking Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 80)
  - United Restaurant Liquor Dealers of Manhattan, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 81)
  - Ace Optical Mfg. Corp., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 82)
  - Ment Brothers Iron Works Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 83)
  - Reicchold Chemical, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 84)
  - 82-10 Queens Blvd., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 85)
  - Art-Lloyd Metal Products Corp., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 86)
  - Blvd. Commercial Body Builders, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 87)
  - Famous Studios, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 88)
  - Coca Cola Bottling Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 89)
  - Morey Machinery Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 90)
  - 1868 Holland Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 91)
  - 2130 Tiebout Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 92)
  - Greenberg Bros, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 93)
  - Bernie Tire Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 94)
  - Concourse Millinery Shop, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 95)
  - Sutton Plaza, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 96)
  - Accurate Steel Rule Die Manufacturers., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 97)
  - Delta Hosiery Shops, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 98)
  - RK Baking Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 99)
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 100)
  - 2460 7th Ave, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 101)
  - 2066 Morris Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 102)
  - Friedland Fixtures, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 103)
  - M. Milman and Sons Furniture Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 104)
  - National Sleep Products, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 105)
  - 1164-58 Vyse Ave, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 106)
  - Feiner's Interiors, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 107)
  - Bernard Fels, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 108)
  - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 109)
  - Uneeda Credit Clothes, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 110)
  - 995 E. 172nd St., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 111)
  - 1705-9 Bathgate Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 112)
  - 555-557 Timpson Place, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 113)
  - 2160 Anthony Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 114)
  - 2145 Matthews Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 115)
  - AL Fenster, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 116)
  - Newmark Lewis, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 117)
  - Widman Bros., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 118)
  - 2014 Morris Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 119)
  - Garment Center Fixture Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 120)
  - Sagamore Cafeteria, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 121)
  - Warshaw Mfg. Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 122)
  - Bernacchia Bros., Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 123)
  - Marino Truckin Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 124)
  - MH Harris and Co., Et Al, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 125)
  - Fink Banking Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 126)
  - Ford Instrument Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 127)
  - Jassem-Silver Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 128)
  - Mica Mfg. Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 129)
  - 1650 Montgomery Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 130)
  - 1385 Shakespeare Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 131)
  - 101 E. 19th St., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 132)
  - The Childs Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 133)
  - Roman Silversmiths, Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 134)
  - 500 West 190 St., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 135)
  - Victory Art Upholstery Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 136)
- A 9504 - A 9955 (1948). (Box 38)
  - Irving Goldberg, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Carlyle Rubber Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Gottfried Baking Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Federal Steel Rule Die Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Wrigley Brothers Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Hanscom Baking Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - La Belle Silver, Inc., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Wheatality Bakery Inc., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Wodan Corporation, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - 797 Crotona Park, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Pearl Dress Shop, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - 1770 Montgomery Ave., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - L and S Casting Co., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Hotel Jefferson and Hotel Division, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Rockwell Mfg. Co, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Super Metal Mfg. Co., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Beach Transit Corporation, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Gates Ambulance Service, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Lion Machine Corporation, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Toasted Pies, Inc., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Namm's, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - 2477 Grand Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Cornell's Apparel Shop, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Acadia Powder Puff Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Shupenko Clothing Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - AI Namm's and Sons, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Portchester Iron Works, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Cavalier Upholstery Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - French American Reeds Manufacturing Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - 775 Union Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - American Spring Products, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Acorn Packaging and Packing Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Gottfriend Baking Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Ward Baking Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - 1821 Bryant Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Epiphone, Inc., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Pur-All Paint Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - J. Blatt Picture Frame Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - City Packaging Corporation, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Hudson Valley Pie Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Mallin Furniture Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Roshevsky and Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Breakstone Brothers, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Eagle Electric Manufacturing Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Gottfried Baking Corporation, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Walsh Pressing Machine Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Olympia Provision and Baking Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - 1878 Harrison Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Sol Blader Sportswear Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Ferro-Co Corporation, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Hanscom Baking Corporation, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - 1982 Walton Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - Phenix Soda Fountain Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - New York and Brooklyn Casket, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - 525 West 138th Street, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - 1154 Ward Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - 1162 Sheridan Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - 1675 East 21st Street, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - 1698 Selwyn Avenue and 3050 Perry Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - 2523 Aqueduct Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - 2775 Kinsbridge Terrace, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - 41-06-50 Street, Long Island, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - Allied Maintenance Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - Jagein Textile Mills, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - 117 South 2nd Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - 1635 Popham Ave., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - City Ice and Fuel Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - Crawford Clothes Inc., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - Western Trawling Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - Mid Island Markets Incorporated, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Tex Ray Fabrics Incorporated, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - 215 East 164th Street, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 72)
  - 1515 Gr. Concourse, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 73)
  - Lumber Industries of Westchester, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 74)
  - JB Salterini Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 75)
  - Coh-Ler Corporation, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 76)
  - Gem Electric Manufacturing Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 77)
  - Murray Bennett Restaurant, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 78)
  - National Cabinet Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 79)
  - Specialty Welding Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 80)
  - Colonial Manufacturing Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 81)
  - ABC Steel and Wire Company, Et Al., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 82)
  - Union Health Center, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 83)
  - American Furniture Frame Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 84)
  - Progressive Restaurant Owners Association, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 85)
  - 2198 Cruger Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 86)
  - 2199 Holland Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 87)
  - Sommerstein's Bakery, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 88)
  - United Mattress Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 89)
  - World-Ware Metal Corporation, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 90)
  - 1255 Webster Avenue, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 91)
  - 2155 Bolton Street, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 92)
  - Bee Line Incorporated, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 93)
  - Manhattan Center, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 94)
  - Parts Manufacturing Company, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 95)
  - Sandell Food, Inc., 1948 (Box 38, Folder 96)
  - Fay's Caf and Restaurant, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 97)
  - Marseilles Hotel, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 98)
  - 700 East 139th Street, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 99)
  - Famous Ski Pants, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 100)